freebookmarkinglist.com 2014-09-26

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the way Free Bookmarking List collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from [user](http://freebookmarkinglist.com/tag/user/ "Posts tagged with user") of the Free Bookmarking List site. This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Free Bookmarking List.

**Personal identification information**  

We may collect personal identification information from Users in many ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as proper, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily give such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information  
**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users when they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers used and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How we use collected information**

FreeBookmarkingList may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * _\- To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature_
  * \- To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
  * _\- To send periodic emails_
  * \- We may use the email address to send User information and updates of their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

**Sharing your personal information**

We **DO NOT sell, trade, or rent** users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information about visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Third party websites  
**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

**Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

**Changes to this privacy policy**

FreeBookmarkingList has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page and send you an email. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to check this privacy policy periodically and become aware of changes.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site after the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

FreeBookmarkingList

http://FreeBookmarkingList.com

Free Bookmarking List  
2333 Driftwood Stu 407  
Mesquite Tx, 75150

privacy_policy@freebookmarkinglist.com

This document was last updated on November 02, 2013
